Oh... Oh...
What is this?
A meatball? Really?
It's always more fun to mess
with Dwight with an audience.
That was usually Pam.
So now that she's out,
I had to find someone else.
Turns out that Stanley
is quite the comedy fan.
But not everything
makes him laugh.
He has very specific tastes.
Through a painstaking process of trial
and error, I found out what he likes.
And it's really weird.
Jim, come on. So juvenile.
What the...
You've been meatballed.
Are you ready
for some meatballs?
Oh, man!
This is not very clever, Jim.
I know.
Look for your stapler.
Really, Jim? Really?
Very funny.
Okay, good night.
What's the haul?
Thirty-two meatballs.
Good day.
That idiot's been
feeding us for a week.
We'll never have to
buy meatballs again.
Dunder Mifflin.
Jessica, hi, how are you?
Yay, that's so great to hear.
I'm not going to be one of
those exes who can't move on.
They have their
life and I have mine.
I'm taking an Italian class.
So far, I have learned tortellini,
spaghettini, linguine.
Well, it's not so much
a class as a restaurant.
But I do Monday, Wednesday,
Friday from 7:00 to 9:00.
I will patch you
through right now.
You sound really
pretty today. Okay.
Jessica, I love you.
That's a message from my mom.
My parents met Jessica, and they
completely flipped for her so,
they gave me this old
family ring to use on her.
I know. Whoa.
Pump the brakes, Bernard.
Too early, I get it.
I just... You know,
I'm just carrying it around,
seeing how it feels.
I haven't proposed
to anyone in years.
Mom took the main diamond out.
She thought that had more of a
"my little brother"
kind of vibe to it. But...
Whoa. It's pretty nice.
Got a little bit of
The Shining vibe, though.
Who needs a house that size?
Big, stupid, pure chump bait.
I'm selling the house,
actually.
No, there's
a glare from over here.
Oh, wow, that's magnificent.
It's mid-recession in a depressed
area of a faltering state,
and I've got the most expensive
house on the market.
The 1% are
suffering too, people.
I bought it to be
my Playboy Mansion.
A temple to wine,
revelry, sex, intrigue.
This was hot on the heels of
Eyes Wide Shut, mind you.
Then I met my wife,
she moved in, made it her own.
Now she's left me and forced
me to sell the place.
The ultimate insult,
they're calling
my speakeasy
lounge a rumpus room.
Does my turmoil
amuse you, Jim?
I'm sorry. I thought
you were making a joke.
What could you possibly have
found funny in what I said?
What was the joke
you thought you heard?
I guess I thought
you were approaching it
with more of
a sarcasm than misery.
Kind of laughing
at your own pain.
Sad clown thing.
Oh, yes. How hilarious it is,
to laugh at clowns, the painted
jesters of a dying circus industry.
Very funny, Jim. I get it.
Um, I'm getting reports of a serious
outbreak of the "grumpies" in here.
A beautiful monster cost me
my 40s and my dream home.
I think I'm entitled to
the occasional bad day.
Well, please tell
Susan we all say hi.
Dude, what if,
since you're feeling grumpy,
we all swing by
tonight and check out
your indoor pool?
Kevin, no.
Like some sort
of last hurrah?
Yeah. All of us in the pool,
saying hurrah.
Maybe the last one
that says hurrah is "it."
Well, I suppose someone
should enjoy the place
before I hand it over to the staging
experts at RE/MAX tomorrow.
Let's try this.
Everyone, tonight, my house,
wear a swimsuit.
Let's just call
it a get-together.
And let's say no food.
Hey, Oscar, was
that you who just
created a party out of
thin air or was it me?
That was you, Kevin.
It was me.
You going tonight, kiddo?
Because I can give you a lift.
Oh, I don't know,
Meredith, it seems like
you shouldn't drive,
maybe ever.
It's no problem.
You live right near me.
How do you know
where I live?
Andy followed you home
after the Christmas party.
Why?
He wanted to make sure
California didn't put it in you.
Oh. Come on.
Wow. Andy's such
a weird stalker.
Following me home like that
when he has a girlfriend,
I should get a restraining order.
It is warm.
It's almost too warm.
I'm feeling 82, 82.5.
Oh. So close. Eighty-one.
Well, we'll say it's 82,
and it'll be our secret.
Hey, late guy-
Hey.
Wow. Just stopping by.
Got another party to go to.
A wife and two kids at home party.
Oh.
DJ Pam Halpert is spinning some
serious Radio Disney tonight.
You're looking at the master
of leaving parties early.
The key is you have to
make a strong impression,
so you want to have a picture taken,
you want to say some peculiar
non sequitur that
people remember,
you want to note something unique,
a talking point for later.
I don't mean to brag, but New
Year's Eve, I was home by 9:00.
Robert, I just wanted to
grab you for one second.
This place is amazing,
by the way.
You should see
the whole thing.
I bet I should.
That's beautiful. I'm going
to e-mail that to you.
I'm just about
to give the tour.
All right. Well.
Join us.
You must see what you
were laughing about.
I must.
Wow.
Yeah, that's some
pretty serious poolage.
What are you doing?
Hmm?
Flicking a bug
off my weiner.
Gross.
I'm getting a drink.
Do you want anything?
No, I'm good.
Funny how you can be surrounded by
people and still feel so lonely.
Hi.
How is everything?
How's your car?
It's great, you know,
reliable, great mileage.
Is that so?
How about this weekend we take that
sucker to a duck pond or something?
Maybe get caught in the rain.
Well, I can't. I'm
going skiing with Jessica.
Couple of dopes
on the slopes.
Oh. Like a goodbye trip.
No. What?
Hey.
Hi.
I guess Andy isn't totally
over his current girlfriend.
But if he was
jealous once before,
then maybe I can
make him jealous again.
Just not with Robert.
He told me he was a ride I wouldn't
survive, and I believe him.
Wow. You made it.
Yeah. Yeah.
Uh-oh. Look at this. Red
plastic cup, red plastic cup.
How about that?
You know, you are
just as dumb at night.
Mmm.
There is...
This would be no problem.
I could swim under one breath!
No! Show me.
All right.
Dive in from here
right now. Okay.
Hey, Dwight Snoot. What you doing?
Wait, relaxing. Scram.
God.
Hey, Stanley,
what happened to my pants?
I moved them. Pants only need a
chair if there's a person in them.
Come on,
don't you want to play?
Oh, really?
Yeah.
You want to play,
you little hick?
Dwight!
- Awesome!
- Dwight!
Here we have
the parlor.
I imagined people
would set down their coats
and symbolically,
their inhibitions.
This was the gateway.
You enter this room a lawyer,
a doctor, a teacher, a judge,
but beyond it, you are simply a
penis, a vagina, a hunger, an ache.
Susan used it as
a Pilates studio.
Holy cow.
My wine collection.
How many bottles?
Three hundred?
About 1,200.
What the hell,
grab a bottle.
Less inventory
for the lawyers.
Toby, Chéteau Margaux, '95.
You know your wine.
Well. And you have a...
Yes, another château.
Robert, you are too kind.
Oh... Too kind doesn't
begin to cover it.
With ammunition like this, we are
in for quite a night, you and me.
And Gabey makes three.
Robert, thank you. Thank you for
this, thank you for all this.
This night's been magical.
Jim, come see
this next room.
I think you
especially would like it.
Really? Why?
I don't know.
Maybe not. Just come.
Do you regret
attacking me now, hick?
Huh? Dwight. Stop it. I
was flirting with you.
I was trying to use
you to make Andy jealous.
I'm not going to help you.
Why would you choose me?
Because I'm mighty?
Because I'm the manliest man
in the office? I'll do it!
Stop.
You stop.
No, you stop.
Is he looking? You can stop.
Okay, you can stop.
No,no,no, he's not looking.
You can actually stop.
Whoa, you guys,
I just found this
insane engagement ring.
Is anyone missing this?
The main stone's missing.
I don't know.
It looks pretty great to me.
I pictured myself
here every night,
eating a leg of
mutton, the juices
dripping down my bare chest,
wiping my fingers on the walls.
Then I met the vegan.
Good night.
To the kitchen.
- Onward.
- Toby,
what's compelling about this
is the note of persimmon.
Right?
Note?
It's a symphony-
Okay.
You have to join my
wine tasting club.
I would love that.
Toby, you are
playing a dangerous game.
I guess I'm through
the gateway now though, right?
You know,
I don't think I've ever been
in this exact angle before.
I'm scared of firsts,
but I like it.
You guys got to
try this pool.
No top scum, no Band-Aids,
this thing is choice.
You in?
Yeah. Sure, sure,
I'll be right in.
I've been working out,
but the problem is, I've been
building muscle underneath
and that top layer
hasn't burned off yet.
Awkward stage.
Mmm.
So good. Now take a chip,
and crush it into my face
and rub the grease around.
Do it. Yeah, rub it in.
Yeah.
That's so good.
Andy's not even looking.
I think sexy eating is a dead end.
Damn it.
What is the most
romantic possible thing?
We can get some chicken fights
going in the pool.
Dwight, that's just...
That's really perfect.
Thank you. Yes.
Yes!
You're in my lane!
Andy,
Dwight and I challenge you
and Jess to a chicken fight.
Winner take all.
Chicken fight!
No,thanks.
Dang it!
What the heck already!
Cathy, chicken fight!
Okay, yeah, who's going to be my partner?
Where's Jim?
I'm right here.
Come on, Cath.
Yes!
Whoo!
Dwight, our chemistry is really clicking.
We work so well together.
I know. I could just
bang you right now.
He's not looking. Hey!
I had two bears sewn together
to make this king size.
Total waste of two bears.
To both these bears.
- To both these bears.
- Bears.
To both these bears.
When I put in the screening
room, I bought three movies.
Caligula, Last Tango in
Paris and Emmanuelle 2.
Mwa!
The last two movies I
actually watched in here were
Marley & Me and
On Golden  Pond.
I mean, it's clearly meant
for watching erotic cinema.
Yeah. We could watch some
right now, if you want.
I've got a Korean
film on my iPod.
If you want to just...
If you have the cables.
Kelly, that's
a crazy ring you found.
Yeah. Thanks, I'm
really glad that I found it.
I can't believe
you're wearing it.
Are you not
superstitious at all?
Of course I'm superstitious,
what are you talking about?
Ring of a failed marriage might
have some sinister energy, right?
Am I just being silly?
I don't think
you're being silly.
Oh, God.
You know what?
I can just sell it
and put the money
in the party fund.
Oh...
Then another woman will get
it, we can't allow that.
We have to destroy it.
Come on. Let's
chicken fight those two.
How was that?
Okay, watch my toes.
Hey, Val, want a beer?
It might taste better than that
pool water you've been drinking.
No, I'm good. Thank you.
Cool.
Does Darryl not swim?
That's racist. I don't know,
but I would say by looking at
him, no, Darryl does not swim.
That's all right! That's all right!
We got this!
Yeah!
Maybe we should take a little break.
Dwight, we've got this.
I promise. I will not leave
your shoulders no matter what.
Okay.
- One more?
- Yeah. Great.
Mush! Mush! Mush!
Come on!
Go!
Here we go.
Yay!
Whoa!
Wow.
I cannot believe you're still on.
I can't believe it either.
I've got this!
Erin, did we win?
Sure. Sure, we did.
You're lying.
We didn't win.
Hey, hey, hey, Dwight! It's okay!
Just rest. Just rest.
You've broken up your last
couple, you evil ring.
Do it.
We're in the pool.
Shove it, Angela.
Same old party,
same old people, am I right?
Reminds me of
Phyllis' birthday.
Ooh. Do not remind me of
Phyllis' birthday. I know.
But boy, that Erin, she sure is
a ripe little tiger, isn't she?
Meow!
And to think I always thought
of her as a second Meredith.
Respectfully, I don't
want us walking into
a similar Angela kind of situation.
Mmm.
So I just want to make sure
that you are completely
100% done with Erin.
Last I checked, I'm with Jessica
and I like to get my monog on.
It's monogamy
for my hog and me.
Not what I asked.
We're done.
Erin and I are over.
Okay.
So then you won't mind if
tonight I just go crazy on her?
Just go nuts...
With sex.
Have at it.
Or take it slow,
whatever you guys work out.
You're an idiot.
Cannonball!
Let's do this.
Oh...
So I kind of stepped on this.
I think it's yours.
Yeah.
Oh. Wow.
How did you know
it was mine?
The Bernard family seal, duh.
Duh.
Sorry if your
special night was ruined.
Oh, whoa, whoa, no,
it's not a special night.
Oh, you weren't
going to do it?
Honestly, Erin,
I don't know what I'm doing.
I just...
I don't know.
Thank you.
Andy's confused.
That's not what I was hoping for.
But it's not so bad either.
I can live with confused.
I get confused.
I totally get confused.
And, of course,
the pool.
Ultimate lubricant
for any wild evening.
It was here that my parties would
have crescendoed into true madness.
To madness.
Madness.
To madness!
Hey, I think you
parked my car in.
Is there any way
you can move your van?
Hey, I'm sorry. When I got
here, I put my keys in a bowl.
Are you serious?
Robert, I want you to know, I'm here
to rock with you as late as you want.
And that goes
double for me.
I'll stay even
later than you'd like.
Toby, I am Bacchus,
god of wine.
And I am Bacchus' friend!
Gentlemen, bear witness,
while I've been
mourning the nights
that never were,
one of them has been
unfolding here before me.
This is no get-together.
This is a party.
Yes!
And there's
my talking point.
Yes, that's it.
Push yourselves, boys.
It's not a party if you don't
do something that scares you.
I need a breather.
You two keep going.
Hey, he's asleep.
We can just leave.
So leave.